树。
Trees.
水果，香料和坚果的承载者。
Growers of fruits, spices and nuts.
荫凉的制造者。
Generators of shade.
鸟，松鼠，考拉的家园。
Home to birds, squirrels, koalas.
有前线士兵在应对气候变化？
Front line soldiers in the fight against climate change?
当然！
You bet!
今天我们讨论一些不一样的事，讨论一下teamtrees.org（植树分队）的使命：
Today we're doing something a little different and talking about teamtrees.org’s mission
到2020年种植2000万棵新树，每捐赠一美元等于
of planting twenty million new trees by 2020, where every donation of one dollar equals
种下一棵树。
one tree.
你可能会问自己“种植2000万棵新树对地球母亲
You might be asking yourself “what would planting twenty million new trees do for the
有什么好处？”
planet?”
先让我们看看每一次给teamtrees的捐赠会产生多大的影响！
Let’s take a look at just how huge an impact each donation to teamtrees will make!
从地衣到蜜蜂再到负鼠，各种各样的生物都把树当做家，只一棵
A wide variety of organisms from lichen to bees to possums call trees home, and just
成熟的橡树就可以容纳多达500种不同的物种！
one single mature oak tree can be home to as many as 500 different species!
地球正在迅速的失去物种—我们正处于大灭绝之中，如果没有
The earth is rapidly losing species--we’re in the middle of a mass extinction, and without
树木让他们回家，更多的动物将面临灭绝的危险。
trees for them to call home, many more animals will be at risk for extinction.
许多动物需要树木作为生活，觅食和提供保护的地方，所以只种一棵树
Many animals require trees as a place to live, to feed, and to provide protection, so planting
就相当于同时建造一座房子、饲养场和苗圃！
just one tree is like building a house, feeder, and nursery all at once!
捐出二十美元种二十棵树就相当于建造一整个动物城！
Donating twenty dollars to plant twenty trees is like building an entire animal city!
乘以一百万，那我们谈论的就是一个具有生物多样性动物
Multiply that by a million and we’re talking about a super metropolis of biodiverse animal
生活的超级大都市。
life.
一项又一项的研究表明，在一片树林或森林中度过一段时间
Study after study shows that spending time in a grove of trees or forest can provide
可以让人恢复情绪上的活力。
emotional rejuvenation.
它可以改善你的情绪，营造平和感，同时减少压力，沮丧
It can improve your mood, creating a sense of peace while reducing stress, depression
和愤怒。
and anger.
日本人甚至对此有个说法：Shirin-yoku或“林中沐浴”。
The Japanese even have a word for this: Shirin-yoku, or ‘forest bathing’.
树木的影响不仅是情感上的，而且是身体上的；研究表明
The effect of trees is not only emotional, but physical; studies have shown that being
在树木中生活不仅可以降低血压，还可以降低与压力有关的激素，
among trees reduces blood pressure as well as lessens stress-related hormones such as
如皮质醇和肾上腺素。
cortisol and adrenaline.
因此，基本上就是说，树木可以使你快乐。
So basically, trees make you happy.
大量的科学研究表明，快乐的人犯罪较少，尤其是
Plenty of scientific research has shown that happier people commit less crimes, especially
暴力犯罪。
violent ones.
我们认为即使只有几棵树的树林也是不错的选择。
We think a grove of even just a few trees would be pretty nice.
2000万棵新树则可能意味着成千上万的新树林，这意味着数百万人能够
Twenty million new trees would mean potentially thousands of new groves, which means millions
定期在森林里沐浴，增加幸福感，减少犯罪。
of people able to take regular forest baths, increasing happiness and reducing crime.
你将成为一名常规的反犯罪斗士。
You'd be a regular crime fighter.
全靠你帮助种植的大树。
All thanks to the trees you helped plant.
树木通过阻挡阳光和遮荫来降低空气温度。
Trees reduce air temperature through blocking sunlight and creating shade.
也通过从叶子向上反射热量来帮助降温。
Trees also help to cool by reflecting heat upwards from their leaves.
当水分从叶子表面蒸发时，会进一步冷却，就像
Further cooling occurs when moisture evaporates from the surface of leaves, just like the
你的身体通过出汗降温一样。
way your body cools down by sweating.
树木可大幅度降温一块区域。
Trees can cool down an area by a lot.
这可不只有几度的单位，有成熟树林的城区在夏季的高温下，
And we’re not talking about just a couple of degrees, urban neighborhoods with mature
比没有树木的城区要凉爽11度。
trees can be up to 11 degrees cooler in summer heat than neighborhoods without trees.
想一想90度（32摄氏度）酷热的一天和79度（26摄氏度）温暖舒适的一天
Just think about the difference between a miserably hot 90 degree day and a warm, comfortable
有什么不同。
79 degrees.
树木还可以使建筑降温，从而限制了对空调的需求，
Trees can also cool down buildings, limiting the need for air conditioning which has the
而空调又有助于节约能源。
added benefit of helping to conserve energy.
研究表明，精心种植的树荫可以减少20%到30%的
Studies have shown that shade from strategically planted trees can reduce the air conditioning
建筑空调的成本。
costs of buildings by 20% to 30%.
试想一下，如果一个普通的家庭在夏天每个月有大约100美元的制冷费，
Just think, if an average home has a cooling power bill of around $100 per month in the
如果在同一栋房子周围种上10棵树，那么可以节省30%的电费，
summer, and if ten trees were planted around that same house then 30% could be saved, then
这意味着在房子周围种上2000万棵树可以节省600万美元的能源成本！
that means 20,000,000 trees planted around homes could save $60,000,000 in energy costs!
所以，如果你不能为这个特殊的原因捐款，请考虑在你的房子
So if you can’t donate to this particular cause, please consider planting a few new
周围种几棵新树。
trees around your house.
他们不仅会是一个美丽的附加物，甚至可能节省未来自己
Not only will they be a beautiful addition, but they might even save your future self
电费单上的一些钱。
some money on your power bill.
树木是理想的隔音材料，因为它们可以通过两种方式减少声音：首先，
Trees are ideal for use as sound barriers because they reduce sound in two ways: First,
它们吸收声音，因为茂密的树枝和树叶很容易吸收
they absorb sound since thick branches and leaves are great at absorbing high
高频噪音。
frequency noise.
其次，树木使声音发生偏转。
Secondly, trees deflect sound.
当声音击中刚性材料时，它会弹回。
When a sound hits rigid material it bounces back.
当声音撞击树枝等柔性材料时，材料振动，
When a sound hits flexible material such as branches, the material vibrates and the sound
声音转变成其他形式的能量。
is transformed into other forms of energy.
一排浓厚的树木可以阻挡多达15分贝的声音，这就像是
A thick row of trees can block as much as fifteen decibels of sound, that’s almost
戴着一副耳塞，但你可以看到一些美丽的绿茵，而不是
like wearing a pair of ear plugs but you have something beautiful to look at instead of
耳朵里嗝耳的泡沫。
uncomfortable foam in your ears.
树木的根系在暴雨期间巩固土壤，防止侵蚀、洪水和泥石流，。
The root systems of trees hold soil in place during heavy rainstorms preventing erosion,
保护人和建筑物的安全
flooding and mudslides, keeping people and buildings safe.
树木也能改善水质，因为它们的根系有助于过滤杂质和
Trees improve water quality too; as their root systems help to filter impurities and
保持土壤中的水分。
retain water in the soil.
这样就可以对地下水位进行补给，最终排入下水道的水更少，
This allows for water tables to be recharged, with less water ultimately ending up in sewers,
并减少了将污染物带入海洋的降雨量。
and diminishing the amount of stormwater carrying pollutants to the ocean.
一棵100英尺高的树在生长季节可以从土壤中吸收11000加仑的水，
A single 100 foot tall tree can take as much as 11,000 gallons of water out of the soil
释放出健康的氧气和清洁的水蒸气。
during its growing season, releasing the water as healthy oxygen and clean water vapor.
这意味着2000万棵树可以过滤掉惊人的2200亿加仑水！
That means twenty million trees could filter a staggering 220 billion gallons!
这足以容纳超过30万个奥林匹克游泳池！
That’s enough to fill more than 300,000 Olympic swimming pools!
人类吸入氧气并呼出二氧化碳；树木则正好相反，它在光合作用过程中吸收和储存二氧化碳，
Humans inhale oxygen and exhale carbon dioxide; trees do exactly the opposite by absorbing
产生并释放氧气作为副产品。
and storing carbon dioxide during photosynthesis which produces and releases oxygen as a by-product.
过量的二氧化碳正在我们的大气中堆积，从而增强了温室效应，
Excess carbon dioxide is building up in our atmosphere, strengthening the greenhouse effect,
并加剧了全球变暖。
and contributing to global warming.
地球上树木越多，吸收和减少的二氧化碳就越多。
The more trees the earth has, the more carbon dioxide is absorbed and mitigated.
树木产生的氧气量取决于几个因素，
The amount of oxygen produced by a tree depends on several factors, including the species
包括树种、健康状况和环境温度。
of tree, its health, and the ambient temperature.
但是，一些典型的计算是，一棵成熟的树每年可以吸收48磅（21.77公斤）的二氧化碳
However some typical calculations are that a single mature tree can absorb carbon dioxide
并释放足够的氧气回到大气中，
at a rate of 48 pounds (21.77 kg) per year and release enough oxygen back into the atmosphere
以支持两个人。
to support two humans.
每年一英亩的树木消耗同样数量的二氧化碳，相当于
One acre of trees annually consumes the same amount of carbon dioxide equivalent to driving
平均行驶26000英里（41842公里）的汽车。
an average car for 26,000 miles (41,842 km).
如果我们假设一英亩有大约300棵树，那么二千万棵新树可以
If we assume that an acre has roughly 300 trees, then twenty million new trees could
消耗一辆每年行驶超过17亿英里的汽车的二氧化碳当量。
consume the carbon dioxide equivalent of a car driving over 1.7 BILLION miles annually!
最后要说的是，除了二氧化碳，树木还吸收其他潜在
Last but not least, in addition to carbon dioxide, trees absorb other potentially harmful
有害污染物，如二氧化硫和一氧化碳。
pollutants, such as sulfur dioxide and carbon monoxide.
树冠起到物理过滤的作用，捕捉灰尘、花粉、
The canopies of trees act as a physical filter, trapping particulates of dust, pollen,
烟雾和微粒。
smoke and smog.
一棵成熟的树每年可以移除高达2.20磅（1.7公斤）的重量，这意味着2000万棵树
A single mature tree removes up to 2.20 pounds (1.7 kg) every year, which means twenty million
可以移除高达4400万磅重量的污染物。
could remove up to 44 million pounds.
不仅如此，研究还表明，与迎风面相比，
And that’s not all, studies have also shown that the dust level in the air can be as much
树的遮风面空气中的粉尘含量可以降低75%。
as 75% lower on the sheltered side of the tree as compared to the windward side.
没人，我们的意思是，没有一个人喜欢空气中的灰尘。
No one, and we mean no one, likes dust in the air.
所以，帮你和你的邻居一个忙，种些树，或者给teamtrees
So do yourself and your neighbors a favor and plant some trees, or donate a few dollars
捐点钱，为你自己和子孙后代净化一下空气。
to teamtrees.org and clean the air for yourself and generations to come.
2019年7月，瑞士的一项研究表明，如果种植了足够的树木，我们就可以阻止气候变化，
In July of 2019 a Swiss study stated that if we plant enough trees we can stop, or at
或者说至少可以严重遏制气候变化。这也是为什么我们致力于帮助
least put a serious dent in climate change, which is why we’re committed to helping
teamtrees完成它的的使命，即到2020年种植2000万棵新树。
teamtrees.org mission to plant 20 million new trees by 2020.
【事图秀】正在参与，你也应该参与！
The Infographics Show is getting involved and you should too!
每捐赠1美元就等于种下了一棵新树，因此要成为这个
Every donation of $1 equals a new tree planted, so become part of something huge
巨大公益的一部分，向世界展示YouTube社区能够团结起来，做一些
with real benefits, and show the world that the Youtube community can come together
不可思议的事。
and do something incredible.
你还在等什么？
So what are you waiting for?
走出去，到teamtrees.org，参与到种植2000万棵新树的
Get out there and be part of the movement to plant twenty million new trees by going
运动中来！
to teamtrees.org!